https://www.corelis.com/about/privacy-policy/

Full Hardware & Software Package
Development Station (Boundary-Scan & ISP Only)
Development Station (JET Only)
Privacy Policy
EWA Technologies, Inc., under its brand name “Corelis Inc.” (“we”, “our” or “us”), may ask you to provide information that personally identifies you or is otherwise personally identifiable in certain circumstances, including for example when you download .pdf files, download evaluation software, download drivers or ask for additional information (“Personal Information”). Examples of Personal Information are your name or business name, mailing address, phone number, fax number, e-mail address, zip code and occupation or industry.
We use your Personal Information for three primary purposes:
To help you quickly find products, services or information on this website.
To help us in providing relevant content.
To alert you to product upgrades, special offers, updated information and other new services.
If you choose not to provide Personal Information, you can still use most of this website. However, you will not be able to access areas that require you to disclose Personal Information.
We will not sell or rent your Personal Information, nor will we share with or provide to third parties your Personal Information unless we have your consent (which may be inferred as being granted based on circumstances of use of this website and specific product requests) and (1) sharing your Personal Information is required to provide the product or service you have requested, or (2) We need to send your Personal Information to resellers which work on our behalf in order to provide you a product or service (which companies will not have any right to use your Personal Information we share with them beyond what is necessary to assist us). We will disclose your Personal Information to the extent required in the event it must respond to subpoenas, court orders or other legal process, or if we find that your actions on this website violate any terms of use, any usage guidelines for specific products or services, or any terms of any license agreements you agree to.
If you do not want us to send you e-mail or postal mail regarding our products or services, you may send email to us and ask to be taken off the our mailing list.
In addition to the foregoing policy, we restrict access to your Personal Information to those employees who reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you, and we maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to guard your Personal Information.
In addition to collecting Personal Information, we may set and access “cookies” on your computer. A cookie is a small amount of data, often including an anonymous unique identifier, that is sent to your computer’s browser from a web site and stored on your hard drive. However, your browser has modifiable preferences which allow you to accept all cookies, reject all cookies, or notify you when a cookie is set. In order to protect your privacy, your browser only permits a web site to access cookies it has sent to you, not the cookies sent to you by other sites.
If you reject all cookies, you may not be able to utilize portions of this website that require you to “sign in” to allow access to the website cookie set on your browser. Nevertheless, this website uses its own cookies, for a limited number of purposes, and all Personal Information that may be included in the cookie is subject to this Privacy Policy. Examples of uses include accessing your Personal Information when you “sign in” so that we can provide you with customized content; keeping track of preferences as you are using this website; estimating and reporting traffic information on this website; and conducting research to improve this website content and services. Other uses may occur.
This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for www.Corelis.com. This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this web site. It will notify you of the following:
What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the web site, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.
What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.
The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.
How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.
Information Collection, Use, and Sharing
We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site (the “Personal Data”). We only have access to/collect Personal Data that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this Personal Data to anyone.
We will use your Personal Data to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your Personal Data with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order. Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.
We are committed to safeguarding the privacy of our website visitors; this policy sets out how we will treat your personal information.
What information do we collect?
We may collect, store and use the following kinds of personal data:
(a) information about your computer and about your visits to and use of this website (including your IP address, geographical location, browser type, referral source, length of visit and number of page views);
(b) information relating to any transactions carried out between you and us on or in relation to this website, including information relating to any purchases you make of our goods or services (including your name, address and email address);
(c) information that you provide to us for the purpose of subscribing to our website services, email notifications and/or newsletters (including name and email address);
(d) any other information that you choose to send to us.
Cookies
A cookie consists of information sent by a web server to a web browser, and stored by the browser. The information is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server. This enables the web server to identify and track the web browser. We use “session” cookies on the website. We will use the session cookies to: keep track of you whilst you navigate the website. Session cookies will be deleted from your computer when you close your browser. We use Google Analytics to analyze the use of this website. Google Analytics generates statistical and other information about website use by means of cookies, which are stored on users’ computers. The information generated relating to our website is used to create reports about the use of the website. Google will store this information. Google’s privacy policy is available at: http://www.google.com/privacypolicy.html.
Our advertisers/payment services providers may also send you cookies. We publish Google Adsense interest-based advertisements on our website. These are tailored by Google to reflect your interests. To determine your interests, Google will track your behavior across the web using cookies. You can view, delete or add interest categories associated with your browser using Google’s Ads Preference Manager, available at: http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/. You can opt-out of the Adsense partner network cookie at: http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html. However, this opt-out mechanism uses a cookie, and if you clear the cookies from your browser your opt-out will not be maintained. To ensure that an opt-out is maintained in respect of a particular browser, you should use the Google browser plug-in available at: http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/plugin. Most browsers allow you to reject all cookies, whilst some browsers allow you to reject just third party cookies. For example, in Internet Explorer you can refuse all cookies by clicking “Tools”, “Internet Options”, “Privacy”, and selecting “Block all cookies” using the sliding selector. Blocking all cookies will, however, have a negative impact upon the usability of many websites, including this one.
Using your personal data Personal data submitted on this website will be used for the purposes specified in this privacy policy or in relevant parts of the website. We may use your personal information to:
(a) administer the website;
(b) improve your browsing experience by personalizing the website;
(c) enable your use of the services available on the website;
(d) send to you goods purchased via the website, and supply to you services purchased via the website;
(e) send statements and invoices to you, and collect payments from you;
(f) send you general (non-marketing) commercial communications;
(g) send you email notifications which you have specifically requested;
(h) send to you our newsletter and other marketing communications relating to our business or the businesses of carefully-selected third parties which we think may be of interest to you by post or, where you have specifically agreed to this, by email or similar technology (you can inform us at any time if you no longer require marketing communications);
(i) provide third parties with statistical information about our users – but this information will not be used to identify any individual user;
(j) deal with inquiries and complaints made by or about you relating to the website; and
(k) OTHER USES. Where you submit personal information for publication on our website, we will publish and otherwise use that information in accordance with the license you grant to us. We will not without your express consent provide your personal information to any third parties for the purpose of direct marketing.
Disclosures
We may disclose information about you to any of our employees, officers, agents, suppliers or subcontractors insofar as reasonably necessary for the purposes as set out in this privacy policy. In addition, we may disclose information about you:
(a) to the extent that we are required to do so by law;
(b) in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings;
(c) in order to establish, exercise or defend our legal rights (including providing information to others for the purposes of fraud prevention and reducing credit risk); and
(d) to the purchaser (or prospective purchaser) of any business or asset which we are (or are contemplating) selling. Except as provided in this privacy policy, we will not provide your information to third parties.
International data transfers
Information that we collect may be stored and processed in and transferred between any of the countries in which we operate in order to enable us to use the information in accordance with this privacy policy. Information which you provide may be transferred to countries (including the United States) which do not have data protection laws equivalent to those in force in the European Economic Areas (EEA). In addition, personal information that you submit for publication on the website will be published on the internet and may be available, via the internet, around the world. You expressly agree to such transfers of personal information.
Security of your personal data
We will take reasonable technical and organizational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information. Of course, data transmission over the internet is inherently insecure, and we cannot guarantee the security of data sent over the internet.
Policy amendments
We may update this privacy policy from time-to-time by posting a new version on our website. You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are happy with any changes. We may also notify you of changes to our privacy policy by email.
Your rights
You may instruct us to provide you with any personal information we hold about you. Provision of such information may be subject to the payment of a fee. You may instruct us not to process your personal data for marketing purposes by email at any time. (In practice, you will usually either expressly agree in advance to our use of your personal data for marketing purposes, or we will provide you with an opportunity to opt-out of the use of your personal data for marketing purposes.)
Third party websites
The website contains links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of third party websites.
Updating information
Please let us know if the personal information which we hold about you needs to be corrected or updated.
Contact If you have any questions about this privacy policy or our treatment of your personal data, please write to us.
The Following Applies to Individuals Whose Personal Data Falls Under the Jurisdictions Subject to the E.U.’s General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR):
Corelis, Inc. is the Data Controller for your Personal Data. Your consent to our use of the Personal Data provides Corelis Inc. with a lawful basis for such use. We will retain the Personal Data indefinitely unless you instruct us to delete it or we inform you otherwise. If you feel that there is a problem with how the Personal Data has been handled, you have the right to register a complaint with a supervisory authority.
Your Access to and Control Over Information
You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website:
See what data we have about you, if any.
Change/correct any data we have about you.
Have us delete any data we have about you.
Express any concern you have about our use of your data.
Security
We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline. Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or looking for “https” at the beginning of the address of the web page. While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.
Do-Not-Track Signals
Our website includes third-party applications that track visitors. The following applications do not respond to Do-Not-Track (“DNT”) requests. Clicking on the links will bring up their privacy policies. Google.com; GoogleAdServices.com. Those applications that do respond to DNT do not drop cookies into visitors’ browsers.
If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately info@corelis.com.
Terms of Use Agreement
Copyright
Unless otherwise indicated, this Web Site and its content, graphics, design, digital conversion and other matters related to the Site are protected under applicable copyright law, trademarks and other proprietary (including but not limited to intellectual property) rights.
The posting of information or materials on the Site does not constitute a waiver of any right in such information and materials. Some of the content on the Site is the copyrighted work of third parties.
Any software or firmware that is made available to download from this web site (“Software/Firmware”) is the copyrighted work of EWA Technologies unless otherwise specified and is protected from unauthorized copying, use or modification by the laws of the United States of America. Use of the Software/Firmware is governed by the terms of the end user license agreement, if any, which accompanies or is included with the Software/Firmware (“License Agreement”). If a License Agreement accompanies or is included with the Software/Firmware, no end user will be able to use or install such Software/Firmware unless it, he or she first agrees to the License Agreement terms. Each License Agreement will be made available electronically or otherwise in advance to the end user for his or her review and either acceptance or rejection.
The Software/Firmware is made available for downloading solely for use by end users according to the License Agreement. Any use, reproduction, redistribution or modification of Software/Firmware outside the scope of or not in accordance with the License Agreement is expressly prohibited.
WITHOUT LIMITING THE FOREGOING, PARTICULARLY ANY LICENSE AGREEMENT, MODIFICATION OF THE SOFTWARE/FIRMWARE, OR THE COPYING OR REPRODUCTION OF THE SOFTWARE/FIRMWARE TO ANY OTHER SERVER OR LOCATION, FOR FURTHER REPRODUCTION OR REDISTRIBUTION IS EXPRESSLY PROHIBITED.
THE SOFTWARE/FIRMWARE IS WARRANTED, IF AT ALL, ONLY ACCORDING TO THE TERMS OF THE LICENSE AGREEMENT. EXCEPT AS WARRANTED IN THE LICENSE AGREEMENT, WE HEREBY DISCLAIM ALL WARRANTIES AND CONDITIONS WITH REGARD TO THE SOFTWARE/FIRMWARE, INCLUDING ALL IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.
THE DOCUMENTS AND RELATED GRAPHICS PUBLISHED ON THIS WEB PAGE MAY CONTAIN TECHNICAL INACCURACIES OR TYPOGRAPHICAL ERRORS. EWA TECHNOLOGIES DISCLAIMS ANY WARRANTY OF TECHNICAL ACCURACY OR FREEDOM FROM ERROR, AND WE SHALL NOT BE LIABLE TO YOU FOR ANY DAMAGES RESULTING FROM SUCH INACCURACIES OR ERRORS. CHANGES ARE PERIODICALLY ADDED TO THE INFORMATION HEREIN. WE MAY MAKE IMPROVEMENTS AND/OR CHANGES IN THE PRODUCT(S) AND/OR THE PROGRAM(S) DESCRIBED HEREIN AT ANY TIME IN ITS SOLE DISCRETION. DESPITE OUR PROVISION OF ANY CHANGES AND/OR IMPROVEMENTS TO THE INFORMATION, PRODUCT(S) OR PROGRAM(S), WE SHALL HAVE NO OBLIGATION TO YOU TO PROVIDE SUCH CHANGES AND/OR IMPROVEMENTS EXCEPT AS MAY BE OTHERWISE PROVIDED.
Links to Third Party Sites
SOME LINKS IN THIS SITE WILL LET YOU LEAVE THE Corelis Inc. SITE. THE LINKED SITES ARE NOT UNDER OUR CONTROL. WE ARE NOT RESPONSIBLE FOR THE CONTENT OF ANY LINKED SITE OR ANY LINK CONTAINED IN A LINKED SITE, OR ANY CHANGES OR UPDATES TO SUCH SITES, AND WE SHALL NOT BE LIABLE TO YOU FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES YOU MAY SUSTAIN AS A RESULT OF YOUR USE OF ANY LINKED SITE. WE ARE PROVIDING THESE LINKS TO YOU ONLY AS A CONVENIENCE TO YOU, AND THE INCLUSION OF ANY LINK DOES NOT IMPLY AND SHALL NOT BE DEEMED AN ENDORSEMENT BY US OF THE LINKED SITE.
Trademarks
All Corelis Inc. product names or brands referenced anywhere in this website and the Corelis Inc. trade name are the registered and unregistered trademarks of EWA Technologies, Inc. The names of parties and other product names or brands of other parties mentioned anywhere in This website may be the trademarks of their respective owners, use of which by us is licensed or otherwise permitted by law.
Any other rights not expressly granted by us herein or in the License Agreement are hereby expressly reserved.
Top
Do NOT follow this link or you will be banned from the site!
Request Technical Support
Complete the form below to request technical support.
Name*
First
Last
Company*Address*
Street Address
Address Line 2
City
State / Province / Region
ZIP / Postal Code
AfghanistanAlbaniaAlgeriaAmerican SamoaAndorraAngolaAnguillaAntarcticaAntigua and BarbudaArgentinaArmeniaArubaAustraliaAustriaAzerbaijanBahamasBahrainBangladeshBarbadosBelarusBelgiumBelizeBeninBermudaBhutanBoliviaBonaire, Sint Eustatius and SabaBosnia and HerzegovinaBotswanaBouvet IslandBrazilBritish Indian Ocean TerritoryBrunei DarussalamBulgariaBurkina FasoBurundiCambodiaCameroonCanadaCape VerdeCayman IslandsCentral African RepublicChadChileChinaChristmas IslandCocos IslandsColombiaComorosCongo, Democratic Republic of theCongo, Republic of theCook IslandsCosta RicaCroatiaCubaCuraçaoCyprusCzech RepublicCôte d'IvoireDenmarkDjiboutiDominicaDominican RepublicEcuadorEgyptEl SalvadorEquatorial GuineaEritreaEstoniaEswatini (Swaziland)EthiopiaFalkland IslandsFaroe IslandsFijiFinlandFranceFrench GuianaFrench PolynesiaFrench Southern TerritoriesGabonGambiaGeorgiaGermanyGhanaGibraltarGreeceGreenlandGrenadaGuadeloupeGuamGuatemalaGuernseyGuineaGuinea-BissauGuyanaHaitiHeard and McDonald IslandsHoly SeeHondurasHong KongHungaryIcelandIndiaIndonesiaIranIraqIrelandIsle of ManIsraelItalyJamaicaJapanJerseyJordanKazakhstanKenyaKiribatiKuwaitKyrgyzstanLao People's Democratic RepublicLatviaLebanonLesothoLiberiaLibyaLiechtensteinLithuaniaLuxembourgMacauMacedoniaMadagascarMalawiMalaysiaMaldivesMaliMaltaMarshall IslandsMartiniqueMauritaniaMauritiusMayotteMexicoMicronesiaMoldovaMonacoMongoliaMontenegroMontserratMoroccoMozambiqueMyanmarNamibiaNauruNepalNetherlandsNew CaledoniaNew ZealandNicaraguaNigerNigeriaNiueNorfolk IslandNorth KoreaNorthern Mariana IslandsNorwayOmanPakistanPalauPalestine, State ofPanamaPapua New GuineaParaguayPeruPhilippinesPitcairnPolandPortugalPuerto RicoQatarRomaniaRussiaRwandaRéunionSaint BarthélemySaint HelenaSaint Kitts and NevisSaint LuciaSaint MartinSaint Pierre and MiquelonSaint Vincent and the GrenadinesSamoaSan MarinoSao Tome and PrincipeSaudi ArabiaSenegalSerbiaSeychellesSierra LeoneSingaporeSint MaartenSlovakiaSloveniaSolomon IslandsSomaliaSouth AfricaSouth GeorgiaSouth KoreaSouth SudanSpainSri LankaSudanSurinameSvalbard and Jan Mayen IslandsSwedenSwitzerlandSyriaTaiwanTajikistanTanzaniaThailandTimor-LesteTogoTokelauTongaTrinidad and TobagoTunisiaTurkeyTurkmenistanTurks and Caicos IslandsTuvaluUSUS Minor Outlying IslandsUgandaUkraineUnited Arab EmiratesUnited KingdomUruguayUzbekistanVanuatuVenezuelaVietnamVirgin Islands, BritishVirgin Islands, U.S.Wallis and FutunaWestern SaharaYemenZambiaZimbabweÅland Islands
Country
Phone*Email*
Product*Select a productCodeRunner-RAD750I2C Exerciser/CAS-1000I2C Exerciser/BusPro-ISPI Exerciser/BusPro-SScanExpress SoftwareJTAG HardwareLegacy ProductOtherModel*Select a productCPXI-1149.1/TurboCVME-1149.1CVXI-1149.1CVXI-1149.1/IMCVXI-1149.5CVXI-JTMCVXI-1149.1/616NetUSB-1149.1/ENetUSB-1149.1/SEPCI-1149.1PCI-1149.1/TurboPC-1149.1/100FPCMCIA-1149.1/EPCMCIA-1149.1PIO-1149.1/EUSB-1149.1/EUSB-1149.1/1EUSB-1149.1/4EOtherSerial NumberLicense NumberSpecify OtherPriorityNot UrgentSlightly UrgentMedium UrgencyIncreased UrgencyUrgentRelated Inquiry NumberReason for Request*Please describe your reason for contacting us in detail.Privacy*
I consent to my submitted data being collected and stored.
Learn More *
EmailThis field is for validation purposes and should be left unchanged.
×
Thanks for reaching out!
We have received your request and would like to thank you for contacting us. We will get back to you as soon as possible.
Talk to you soon,
The Corelis Team
CLOSE
Register for Training
Please provide the requested information to register for a training class at our facility in Cerritos, California.
Name*
First
Last
Company/Organization*TitleEmail*
Phone*Address*
Street Address
Address Line 2
City
State / Province / Region
ZIP / Postal Code
AfghanistanAlbaniaAlgeriaAmerican SamoaAndorraAngolaAnguillaAntarcticaAntigua and BarbudaArgentinaArmeniaArubaAustraliaAustriaAzerbaijanBahamasBahrainBangladeshBarbadosBelarusBelgiumBelizeBeninBermudaBhutanBoliviaBonaire, Sint Eustatius and SabaBosnia and HerzegovinaBotswanaBouvet IslandBrazilBritish Indian Ocean TerritoryBrunei DarussalamBulgariaBurkina FasoBurundiCambodiaCameroonCanadaCape VerdeCayman IslandsCentral African RepublicChadChileChinaChristmas IslandCocos IslandsColombiaComorosCongo, Democratic Republic of theCongo, Republic of theCook IslandsCosta RicaCroatiaCubaCuraçaoCyprusCzech RepublicCôte d'IvoireDenmarkDjiboutiDominicaDominican RepublicEcuadorEgyptEl SalvadorEquatorial GuineaEritreaEstoniaEswatini (Swaziland)EthiopiaFalkland IslandsFaroe IslandsFijiFinlandFranceFrench GuianaFrench PolynesiaFrench Southern TerritoriesGabonGambiaGeorgiaGermanyGhanaGibraltarGreeceGreenlandGrenadaGuadeloupeGuamGuatemalaGuernseyGuineaGuinea-BissauGuyanaHaitiHeard and McDonald IslandsHoly SeeHondurasHong KongHungaryIcelandIndiaIndonesiaIranIraqIrelandIsle of ManIsraelItalyJamaicaJapanJerseyJordanKazakhstanKenyaKiribatiKuwaitKyrgyzstanLao People's Democratic RepublicLatviaLebanonLesothoLiberiaLibyaLiechtensteinLithuaniaLuxembourgMacauMacedoniaMadagascarMalawiMalaysiaMaldivesMaliMaltaMarshall IslandsMartiniqueMauritaniaMauritiusMayotteMexicoMicronesiaMoldovaMonacoMongoliaMontenegroMontserratMoroccoMozambiqueMyanmarNamibiaNauruNepalNetherlandsNew CaledoniaNew ZealandNicaraguaNigerNigeriaNiueNorfolk IslandNorth KoreaNorthern Mariana IslandsNorwayOmanPakistanPalauPalestine, State ofPanamaPapua New GuineaParaguayPeruPhilippinesPitcairnPolandPortugalPuerto RicoQatarRomaniaRussiaRwandaRéunionSaint BarthélemySaint HelenaSaint Kitts and NevisSaint LuciaSaint MartinSaint Pierre and MiquelonSaint Vincent and the GrenadinesSamoaSan MarinoSao Tome and PrincipeSaudi ArabiaSenegalSerbiaSeychellesSierra LeoneSingaporeSint MaartenSlovakiaSloveniaSolomon IslandsSomaliaSouth AfricaSouth GeorgiaSouth KoreaSouth SudanSpainSri LankaSudanSurinameSvalbard and Jan Mayen IslandsSwedenSwitzerlandSyriaTaiwanTajikistanTanzaniaThailandTimor-LesteTogoTokelauTongaTrinidad and TobagoTunisiaTurkeyTurkmenistanTurks and Caicos IslandsTuvaluUSUS Minor Outlying IslandsUgandaUkraineUnited Arab EmiratesUnited KingdomUruguayUzbekistanVanuatuVenezuelaVietnamVirgin Islands, BritishVirgin Islands, U.S.Wallis and FutunaWestern SaharaYemenZambiaZimbabweÅland Islands
Country
How did you hear about us?*Social AdSocial PostGoogle SearchNewsletterWebinarTrade ShowSales Rep / DistributorI am a Current CustomerPreferred Training Session*Please select your preferred training session dates.November 10-12, 2020CommentsPrivacy*
I consent to my submitted data being collected and stored.
Learn More *
CAPTCHA
CLOSE
